Luke Nemy

♥ Honolulu, Hawaii, United States ■ lukenemy7@gmail.com 🛘 (510)-681-6419 🛅 https://www.linkedin.com/in/luke-nemy/

▲ https://luke-nemy.netlify.app

SUMMARY

Software developer with 5 years of experience developing enterprise level applications in ReactJS, Python, and Ruby on Rails. Proven understanding of Agile development methods and DevOps practices. Proven understanding of test driven development, hosting management and API integreations.

PROJECTS

Mongo Blog

October 2022 - October 2022

- · Personal dev blog built using MERN stack; includes React Hooks w/ context API and Mongoose ODM w/ Mongo Atlas DB.
- · Implemented JWT for Auth and measures to ensure single user registration; hosting frontend on Netlify and backend on Heroku.
- · Complete deployed site from concept to production in one week.

Gentle Scratches Tattoo

October 2022 - Present

· Currently developing PWA appointment booking app using Vite + Preact, Firebase Storage and Square API.

EXPERIENCE

Remote Full Stack Developer

Hayes & Co

May 2022 - Present, Remote

- MERN stack app development w/ React 18 including Redux Toolkit and JWT Auth.
- · Created websites for multiple clients using Wordpress w/ Elementor Pro and Figma prototyping/wireframes.
- · Database management for Slack app.

Safe Travel Hawaii Technical Service

eWorld Enterprise Solutions

November 2020 - April 2021, Honolulu, Hi

- · Provided support for travelers using Safe Travels Hawaii Contact Tracing Program for entering the State of Hawaii during Covid-19 pandemic.
- · Resolved various technical bugs and user error tickets using ServiceNow platform.
- · Created apps with ServiceNow Developer.

Frontend Developer Intern

Threshold.co

January 2020 - April 2020, Remote

- · Platform for increasing visibility, bookings at brick-n-mortar venues, and global fanbase tracking and communication.
- · Full PWA architecture w/ Preact, Firebase, GraphQL, Parcel, Google Maps & Stripe API (SCA Compliance).
- · Building frontend features for Artists, Venues and Fan facing pages.

Freelance Wordpress Developer

Good Will Hacking

November 2018 - Present, Remote

- Developing client websites using variety of plugins including: Elementor, Woocommerce, Astra Themes, WP Statistics, Yoast SEO, Schedulicity, WP SMTP, WP Cerber, and Contact Form 7.
- · Experience with editing PHP within plugins; hosting with Siteground and Cloudflare caching and site optimization.

EDUCATION

Graduate of Full Stack Software Development Program

Rithm School · San Francisco

Associates in Arts Degree Cultural Anthropology

Berkeley City College · Berkeley, Ca

Graduate of Full Stack Javascript Program

Learners Guild · Oakland, Ca

SKILLS

Javascript ES6 (OOP), Python3, SQL, MongoDB, Java (Android) HTML, CSS (Flexbox/Grid), Ruby (Haml), React, Preact, Redux, React-Native, Node, Flask, Rails, Firebase, SQLAlchemy, PostgreSQL, GraphQl, Jasmine, Jest, Bootstrap4, TailwindCSS, Mongoose, Git, npm, Wordpress, Figma, Adobe Cloud, Zoho CRM, Asana, Slack, Google Analytics